Join Brooklyn Barbie and Malibu Barbie on an underwater adventure.
Barbie: Mermaid Power is a animation, family film directed by Ron Myrick.
Barbie 'Brooklyn' Roberts, Barbie 'Malibu' Roberts, and sisters Skipper, Stacie, and Chelsea go on an
underwater adventure as they transform into mermaids to help save the world of Pacifica.
Malibu (Barbie) (voice), played by America Young.
Brooklyn (Barbie) (voice), played by Tatiana Varria.
Skipper (voice), played by Kirsten Day.
Stacie / Mermaid 1 (voice), played by Cassandra Lee Morris.
Chelsea (voice), played by Natalie Lashkari.
Marlo / Mermaid 2 (voice), played by Melanie Minichino.
Barbie: Mermaid Power or Barbie Mermaid Power is a 2022 CGI-animated musical adventure comedy
children's television film directed by Emory Ronald "Ron" Myrick and written by Ann Austen.
The 40th entry in the Barbie film series, it debuted in Australia on 9Go!
on 17 August 2022 before its release in the United States and globally on
Netflix a fortnight later alongside an accompanying soundtrack album.
The film also had theatrical releases in the British Isles
and Europe throughout October and November.
The film explores themes of magic, mermaid, based on
toy, female protagonist, 3d animation.